Our days of hardship continue.
All the members of our race are mighty individually,
yet as a pack we find ourselves in grave danger.
According to a human scholar named Darwin,
it is not the strong who survive.
It is those who can best adapt to their environment.
The world will soon change greatly,
but there is no reason for us to adapt.
We will change the world to fit us.
It's about time. Are you ready?
Let's play this thing real loud.
I think we'd be better off keeping it mellow.
You're one to talk, Yuliy.
It is now only a matter of time.
To the prosperity of our clan and a new beginning...
A toast!
Hey, wait a second!
Stop right there!
Philip, it's time!
Gei ni.
I play this one way better.
Lord Kershner...
Yes, I know.
How inconvenient it is that we must imitate humans
every time we wish to cross the sea.
I've also received word that the Jaegers have learned of our presence here.
Oh? If we have guests, then it is only common courtesy that I entertain them.
I believe that Lord Yevgraf would not wish us to shed
pointless blood with such a grand task ahead of us.
Perhaps. And our negotiations here in Shanghai were tiring, I must admit.
I will leave this to the others.
That bartender tried to rip me off!
Dude, you should invite me along next time you want to go on a rampage.
For goodness sake.
Everyone stay sharp.
Our performance is starting right on schedule.
There's a lot of pricey-looking gals in that party.
Do you think Kershner's really in there?
Either way, let's split into groups,
just like the Professor planned.
I smell blood.
Yuliy!
That dumbass!
Well, here we go.
Looks like Kershner's not here.
Yuliy!
Don't just run off by yourself like that! Do you want to die?
It worked out just fine.
You and your death wish!
Death wish?
Maybe he doesn't value his life that highly.
You brought your own flair to the job, as always.
I'm sorry for not following the plan.
Yuliy, we are a cooperative pack.
We each contribute what the rest of us lack.
By doing that, we can chase our prey wherever they flee, corner them, and eliminate them.
That's our job.
I am a Jaeger.
And I am...
They're in this room.
You okay?
What a way to kill someone.
I thought this might be the Hyakko Party's doing,
but with them ripped apart like this, it's gotta be Kuratake.
We sure are standing out.
Really? I doubt that foreigners are that rare these days.
Maybe they've all been enchanted by my body.
I bet!
The way all that meat hangs off you is just...
Oh querido.
This is a country that was slaughtering
any and all "barbarian" visitors until recently, after all.
That's not a pleasant thought.
Do you find it nostalgic?
No, this is the first time I've come to Japan.
Are you the party from V Shipping?
I'm a servant of the Naoe household.
Ah, um, welcome to...
Thank you for picking us up.
My friends! We can no longer turn a blind eye to the recent collapse of public order in our capital!
The jailbreak of a feared criminal, the activities of the Hyakko Party...
That will be 14 sen.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Disperse! Disperse!
What do you think you're doing without a permit?
What's the meaning of this?!
Where do you think you are?
They're making a scene.
It almost looks like bullying.
Major Iba, the police have determined that this morning's incident was the work of the escapee.
Not the Hyakko Party, then.
No. There were none of their telltale pamphlets at the scene, either.
There's no question in my mind that it was Kuratake.
You shouldn't express such confidence with so little information, Mochizuki.
Yes, sir!
Also, could you not call me Major when I'm out of uniform?
I don't like drawing attention.
Yes, sir! My apologies!
That's enough.
Your skills grow ever stronger, Miss Ryouko.
Then how well do you think I might fare against that infamous escapee, Sensei?
As the saying goes, Miss Ryouko,
a wise man keeps away from danger.
It's good that you are—
Who are they?
Oh, those would be the Baron's guests.
Members of an international shipping company, I believe.
I cannot put into words my gratitude toward V Shipping for
your assistance when we were involved in the war in Europe.
I would be most pleased if I were able to repay that debt here.
Thank you very much.
I must say that you all are quite proficient in Japanese!
Our work necessitates it.
I admit I've not come here in a while, but even then it seems almost like a new country.
I'd say it really is a new country.
That's how much our economy and industry have advanced.
It's just...
At present, the hearts of all who live in the capital are restless with fear of the night.
I'd very much like to hear more.
Your rooms will be in this annex.
Hey, don't leave me behind!
Give a guy in the bathroom some time to do his business!
Huh? Where's Yuliy?
He said "I smell flowers" and ran off.
Hello! Do you like flowers?
I'm Naoe Ryouko, the Baron's daughter.
I'm Yuliy.
Yuliy!
What a wonderful name!
Do you like the garden? We grow all kinds of imported flowers here.
We bring in fertilizer and pesticides from overseas as well.
This Western-style garden is my father's pride and joy!
You've pampered the flowers too much.
They've been given too much water and fertilizer,
and they're starting to rot from the roots.
The Hyakko Party is an anti-government organization.
They claim that they act to save the poor and bring back the lost samurai spirit to Japan,
but in truth they're just a band of robbers who target only the wealthy.
And then there's the escaped death row inmate, Kuratake Gouichirou.
He's a murderer who was known for exclusively targeting young men,
and he has already killed several people since his escape.
Two gruesome crime sprees occurring at the same time.
Hardly a coincidence, I imagine.
Oh, it's nothing that should trouble you.
So sweet! This stuff's great, Dorothea!
I'll have some later.
Suit yourself.
This luxurious scent reminds me of my homeland in Ireland.
Homesick?
Doesn't really fit your looks.
Hey, do you really think Kershner came here?
We just happened to miss him in Shanghai.
There's no way V Shipping's information is wrong.
What business does he even have out here in the Far East?
Food, maybe?
He came all the way to Japan just to feed?
Way too much time and effort.
It's probably nothing a human could comprehend.
Our prey has their own world.
Our two worlds may collide,
but they'll never overlap.
You're an expert on that topic after all, Yuliy.
Going out to poke around again?
Like a pup?
Sorry, did I hit a nerve?
Come on you two, get along!
We're a team, aren't we?
Get off me!
Stop touching my hair!
Take that! How do you like that?
Don't treat me like a kid!
I see you're getting along.
Is that what this looks like to you, Professor?
Get some rest today.
We're going to be busy starting tomorrow.
All right. I'll speak with you later, then.
You heard what happened this morning, Major Iba?
Yes, sir!
Do you believe that the Hyakko Party is connected with Kuratake's jailbreak?
Having examined some of the investigation documents, I find that unlikely.
And then there's the rumors that Home Affairs has granted
free rein to that shady group of foreigners.
I don't believe that the military can afford inaction in this matter.
I believe that we of the Ninth Floor Annex would be fit for this task.
Indeed. Home Affairs must remain ignorant of our actions at all costs, after all.
At the end of the day, one might say that stepping on their toes is our specialty.
I had to strong-arm the Harbin Special Service Office into sending you back here.
I hope that you can fulfill the expectations I have for you.
Yes, sir!
When can you begin?
We already have.
We will return to pick you up at the appointed time, Lady Agatha.
Thank you.
Why would you break me out of jail
only to throw me down here?
Oh, are you frightened?
A murderer like you?
Are you... going to kill me?
You have an important role to play.
We even know what he looks like!
How can he kill this many people and still slip through our fingers?!
We've never had reason to think that he has accomplices!
Listen up! We're going to double the number of patrolling officers starting tonight!
Inspector!
Don't let him get away with this for another night!
Shut up! What do you want?
Well, uh... I was just told that...
V Shipping?
The Chief has explained the situation to me, Mister Willard.
I was told that the Ministry of Home Affairs has asked us to fully cooperate with you.
Thank you very much.
Let's have a look, then.
Yes, of course.
Might I ask exactly who you all are?
Just think of us as allies of justice who've come to you from across the sea.
Let's see, all that's left on the patrol is...
Before he was caught,
Kuratake targeted only young men.
But his targets after the breakout have been of both genders and all ages.
That's a pretty dramatic shift in behavior.
The police think he's had to lower his standards because he's on the run,
but is that really the case?
Should we really be letting such shady foreigners look at our reports?
That's what the brass wants.
Nothing I can do about it.
Inspector, there's been a murder in Akasaka!
What?!
It better not have been him again!
Let's meet up with the others.
So far as I can tell from the reports,
the Hyakko Party has nothing to do with Kuratake's jailbreak or murders.
What did you see at the prison?
It would be hard for someone to get out with no help.
But there's no evidence of him having any accomplices.
I did dig up some secondhand reports of "flying people."
But they're just being treated as drunken hallucinations.
The police have been increasing their patrols
yet still haven't caught the culprits.
They can't catch them
because they're chasing Kuratake.
He isn't the killer?
I doubt he's even alive.
Then the ones who broke him out of jail and framed him for the killings are...
Them.
Our prey.
The police...
Excuse me?
The police are too focused on finding Kuratake,
a man whose face they know.
So of course they'd never find a woman to be suspicious.
What might you be talking about?
I haven't a clue what—
But I can smell it.
Exuding from your whole body...
a smell like rusty metal and rotten fish.
The smell of blood.
A smell that makes me want to throw up.
The scent of a vampire!
You're a Jaeger!
Hey!
What are you doing over there?
Hey, stop right there!
Does that old man really look tasty to you?
Good work, everyone.
Those damned Jaegers followed us all the way to Japan!
Don't let them lose us, Fallon!
Leave it to me!
Yuliy!
Don't do shit like that! We're not a circus!
Can you get us closer to them?
What do you think I'm doing?
Crap! Hurry up and get us going again, Fallon!
I'm trying!
You filthy Jaeger!
Impossible! You're one of the Sirius?
She's a Royal!
Yuliy!
Don't chase too far! Yuliy!
If I'm to live by inertia
There's probably nothing wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
Enter.
There are Jaegers in Japan, you say?
Yes. I've been told that Agatha was injured.
As I would expect of them.
They have quite the nose.
We can't do anything!
Mister Willard of V Shipping.
That Royal from the other day...
A bit longer. Just a bit longer, Saki.
An artificial heart?
You mangy Sirius!